{
    "subject": "resource/Will_Haven",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Will Haven is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866999387741089,
            "question": "Is Will Haven's hometown in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9724113941192627,
            "question": "If Will Haven's hometown is the United States, what state could it be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9192957878112793,
            "question": "What is the hometown of Will Haven?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.731733500957489,
            "question": "What are some popular cities in Will Haven's hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7049939036369324,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Will Haven based on his hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5691226720809937,
            "question": "Based on his hometown, what cultural events might Will Haven participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3611892759799957,
            "question": "In what country was Will Haven born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3473872244358063,
            "question": "Can you tell me where Will Haven is from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33177366852760315,
            "question": "Does Will Haven live in a different country than where he was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2688008248806,
            "question": "Where does Will Haven call home?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Will Haven is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8767_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Will Haven live in a different country than where he was born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8767_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me where Will Haven is from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8767_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country was Will Haven born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8767_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8767_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document mentions that Will Haven is a noise metal band from Sacramento, California. Sacramento is a city in the United States, so it can be inferred that their hometown is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states Will Haven is from the United States, but text one clearly says they are from Sacramento, California.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}